I keep seeing people ask the heinous question, what did Cassie do? There must be more to the
story. And I just want to use that as a reference point for the bigger conversation
of the fact that whatever you do is your responsibility. There is absolutely
accountability to be taken by people to influence, to manipulate, to provoke 1000%.
Nonetheless, it is still you in the driver's seat. And when we see someone who is in a dominant position
because of their physical ability, their economic ability, their mental capacity, etc.
When we see that person exercising zero control, the question should never be,
what did they do to cause this? The question should be, what is this person not doing
to stop this? When we say that the they're just taking a black man down rhetoric is supporting
white supremacy, what we mean is the failure to ask black men in particular, what are they doing
to stop this is not liberating them. It is actually incriminating them and inciting the idea that they
don't have control and don't need to.